# **Tray Fleary**

Certified: Software Engineer/ Web Developer

Portfolio: tflearydev.github.io

Greater Atlanta Area **(678) 713-1077** 

tflearydev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/trayfleary/ github.com/tflearydev twitter.com/tflearydev

# **Professional Experience (4+ years)**

# Daimler/ Mercedes-Benz USA (Lab 1886) - Innovation Sector

Sep 2019 - Present (van2share.netlify.com - NOT the live app - Demo - use "aaa" for email)

- <u>Leading Front End Development</u> for production application (van2share mobile responsive application where users can find and book Mercedes Sprinter Vans + other vehicles, and unlock/lock directly from the application.)
- Built out front-end of entire application, plus two different B2B facing use cases while onboarding customers.
- Continuing to work throughout the company on different projects + new ideas.

#### DRAPED(E-Commerce), Web Developer & Designer

May 2017- Sep 2019 - (www.DrapedOfficial.com)

- Led the <u>build</u>, <u>customization</u>, <u>and responsible for updating</u> the site's functionality and design using with JS, jQuery, HTML, and CSS + frameworks.
- Also Including: content management, product cards and add to cart- checkout, promotion and discount codes, blog integration, and SEO

# Self-Employed, Freelance Web Developer & Designer (\*see Github)

Jan 2019 - Sep 2019 (tflearydev.github.io)

• Creating Full Stack <u>Javascript and React applications</u>, along with CMS apps.

# Presidential Automotive, Manager/ Developer

Aug 2015 - Aug 2017 (Promotion 2016: Manager / Developer)

- Developed a simple <u>customer-vehicle management application</u> (that wasn't asked of me-not required) to keep track of their customers, cars on the lot, and shops nearby, which <u>earned me a PROMOTION</u>.
- Maintained vehicle-management system along with website and daily ops.

## General Assembly, Software Engineer

 850+ hours of more JavaScript, jQuery, React, Bootstrap, Node, MongoDB, JSON, MVC, RESTful web services, Express.js and more

#### **Full Stack / Git Version Control**

#### Van2share (Github)-https://github.com/tflearydev/van2share

- Find & Book Mercedes Sprinter Vans, + unlock and lock vehicle from app.
- JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Laravel

## Startup Investor App (Github) - https://github.com/tflearydev/StartupRocket

- Startups and investors can create their profiles and connect.
- JS, React.js, Bootstrap & Styled Components, Node, Mongo, Express

# Vehicle Manager App (Github) - https://github.com/tflearydev/VehicleManager

- Businesses can manage daily ops (customers, vehicles, & more)
- JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS, Node, Express, Mongo

# Collectables App (Github) - https://github.com/tflearydev/SneakerCollect

- Allows collectors to buy/sell/trade their collectables
- JavaScript, React.js, HTML, CSS, Node, Mongo, Express

#### **Skills**

HTML | CSS | Vanilla JavaScript | jQuery | React.js | Node.js | MongoDB | JSON | Express.js | MVC | CRUD | Git | Github | ES5 | ES6 | XD | Bootstrap | REST API | Agile Methods | SCRUM | MySQL | SASS | CMS | Wordpress | Shopify | Debugging | Database Management | AWS | Photoshop | Illustrator | Business Development |

#### **Summary**

Creative Front End Developer focused on enhancing the user experience and creating scalable applications, using the best – in demand practices + principles. Passionate for the JavaScript stack on the front-end + back-end, along with being well experienced in the technologies above.

#### **Awards**

Web Development Excellence - 2019

#### **Education**

#### **General Assembly:**

Thrived in a 3+ month, 800+ hour software development immersive program

# Georgia State University:

Transfer, nearing BBA in Business Admin & Management

# North Carolina State University:

Initial college education, studying business